https://aahumboldtdelnorte.org/website-privacy-policy

Meeting Guide App
Resources for Setting Up/Running an Online Meeting:
Website Privacy Policy
Collection and Use of Non-Personal InformationOur server logs information about visitors, including IP addresses, date/time visited, referring website, length of stay, etc. This information is used for site statistics only.
Collection and Use of Personal InformationYou can visit this website without revealing any personal information. However, if you choose to send us an email using the contact form, you will need to enter your name and email address so we can reply to you.  We will not share, give, sell, or offer your email address to anyone else.  We do not maintain an email mailing list, nor do we broadcast information to those who have sent us email.  We dislike spam as much as anyone, and work to prevent it.
ConsentIf you do not consent to the collection of your personal information as outlined above, please do not use our contact form. If you have provided personal information to us in the past via this website and no longer wish for us to keep that information, please notify us.
SecurityNo data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, we do our best to protect your privacy and security. We are serious about data security, to the point of setting up physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to secure any information you may send us. Your personal information will be safeguarded from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures.
External Site LinksIf this website links to other websites on the internet, content and Privacy Policies are the responsibility of their respective owners.
Changes to this Privacy PolicyWe may at any time, without notice to you and in our sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of this website after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.
Printable version
Events Calendar
« October 2020
»
Proudly powered by WordPress.
